<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>A new beginning on yidi</title>
    <link>https://yidi-earth.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in A new beginning on yidi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yidi-earth.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Why Convivial?</title>
      <link>https://yidi-earth.github.io/posts/guten_tag/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yidi-earth.github.io/posts/guten_tag/</guid>
      <description>(This is part of the series L&amp;rsquo;Only Child Syndrome)
An initiative I&amp;rsquo;m living in the void of time and space. I have arrived at a still point in life. As if I&amp;rsquo;m standing in front of this tranquil and magnificent palace. The exquisite details and lifelike reliefs marks its significance as a piece of artwork. A comprehension of mortality, hence immortality. I have always suspected my whole life that I am destined for this place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The revolution will be complete when the language is perfect</title>
      <link>https://yidi-earth.github.io/posts/language-perfect/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yidi-earth.github.io/posts/language-perfect/</guid>
      <description>## The Question Why do you like the things you do? Think about it. Do you actually have any free will over your choice?
Why do you prefer Pepsi over Coca Cola? What if this was a world without Cola at all?
For a while I wanted to rewire the reward system in my brain by lying to myself. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t a very smart idea. I was very proud of being a brain hacker though.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nudity</title>
      <link>https://yidi-earth.github.io/posts/nudity/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yidi-earth.github.io/posts/nudity/</guid>
      <description>He moved over to the window Lorem markdownum comes; pro est modo famulus, quo quod neu manibus aether his nomine, Aurora, voce. Ipse virga res vidit profanis vocatos, quod vestigia cineres, dum silva in vapor. Tendite caelestibus quam, sub inplet prole eveniet superi rus proles venenis potestas Tereo pluribus sunto.
Perque cessisse, hoc tum auras sinuosa. Pressant nec vinci primoque quoque funibus est: et tempore vetitorum? Coercet tantum adsensibus religata protinus venturas et Achilli, nat iam cum deque.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://yidi-earth.github.io/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yidi-earth.github.io/pages/about/</guid>
      <description>What am I fascinated by now? Ritual / Culture Design [The Power of Ritual] (https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/46258506-the-power-of-ritual) by Casper ter Kuile. Conscious Evolution [Consious Evolution] (https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/183673.Conscious_Evolution) by Barbara Marx Hubbard
Where am I? Berlin, Germany
 Home CODE Forests  What do I care? building up on a movement [Convivial Earth] (https://cvvl.earth)
A quote from me  Every day is an invitation to joy
 A thought that haunts me today Time management for mortals: if I live up to 80 years old, I have 17*** days left to live.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
